I have a problem, I can't get access to the error database at a consistent rate
我有困难，我不能持续稳定使用误差数据库
Oh, that is not an impediment
哦，那不是什么障碍
In this retrospective today, I've got list of 10 improvements I'd like you guys to address for the next sprints
在今天的回顾会上我希望你们下个Sprint中从事我提供的十个改进工作
Hey Khara, I'm gonna need you guys to get more work in progress, it's pretty good but you gonna need more stuff than that
卡拉，我希望你们开展更多项的工作，你们做得还不错但是你们可以做得比这个要多
Ok
好
Cool, thanks!
好的，谢谢
Awesome, guys! That's our fastest standing up yet, it was only 40 minutes
太棒了！这是我们最快的一次站立会，只有40分钟
Yeah
是啊
The point is not getting...
关键不是……
I was just reading this and it says Scrum is all that going faster, what's taking you so long?
我刚读完这本书，上面说Scrum会让工作加速，为什么你们还是那么慢？
Get back to work...
继续工作……
There is no way this story is a 13, this is more like a 2.
这个用户故事用13个点不太可能，这更像是两个点的工作
Alright, so we'll kick off this retrospective with 5 minutes silent writing
好，我们就以5分钟的默写来开始回顾会议
Silent writing
默写，不要出声
That's not an impediment
那个并不是障碍
As your ScrumMaster and product owner, these are the stories I need you to commit this sprint
作为你们的ScrumMaster和产品负责人，这些是我希望你们在这个Sprint中承诺的用户故事
My computer was stolen during a break in last night, I can't get any work done until I get a new one
我的电脑昨晚被偷了，在得到新电脑前我没法工作
Have you heard of paper?
你知道可以用纸吗？
Adam, I'm gonna need this feature demo this afternoon, you can get it done right?
亚当，今天下午我要这个特征的演示，你可以做完吧？
Yeah, no problem
好，没问题
Great
很好
I'm just gonna add this to your work in progress
我把这个加入到你们的在进行工作中
Continuous integrations never helps anybody,let's skip that
持续集成就没发挥过作用，我们就省了吧
Oh no Chris, listen, we're doing Scrum now, so we don't have to share that sort of stuff to the management
哦不是这样克里斯，我们现在用Scrum，所以就不用向管理层汇报这种事情
3 months and management think we can get it done in another sprint, and I just don't understand...
三个月时间，管理层以为我们下个Sprint就可以完成工作，我不明白……
Hey guys, surprise! our CEO is joining us for today's retrospective, but just do everything normally...
大伙注意了，我们的CEO来参加今天的回顾会议，会议照常进行……
Hey guys, you are totally failing, so I am gonna cut this sprint a couple of days short
你们的工作太不理想了，所以我决定把这个Sprint减掉几天
Where are you going?
你要去哪儿？
Bio?
上厕所
Do you have a task for that?
你有那些任务吗？
No
没有
Alright guys, you guys are letting our company down this sprint
这个Sprint你们让公司失望了
I was just thinking you guys have a lot to do this sprint so let's make this sprint 3 weeks instead of 2, let's just change that
我只是想这个Sprint你们有好多的工作，那我们就把两周的Sprint改成三周吧，就这么办吧
Cool
好吧
Disagree or commit?
不同意还是承诺？
That's not an impediment
那不是障碍
So we call this story done?
我们可以把这个用户故事当作完成了？
That's close enough, you guys have it
够好了，那我们就完成了
You guys are doing great this sprint but the other team's velocity is a little bit higher, could you pick it up just a little bit?
这个Sprint大家表现都不错，但是另一个团队的速率要稍稍比我们的高，你们可不可以提高一点点？
5 minutes of silent writing
5分钟默写
Hey, no it is a fine time, I'm just doing a retrospective, a job at Google? Yeah
好，没事儿，我只是在开回顾会议，有谷歌工作机会？好的
I'm not gonna be here tomorrow, so if you guys can just do your daily Scrum by email just at whatever time you like, just shoot out email
我明天不在，你们可以通过邮件随便找个时间开每日例会，就发发邮件
That's not an impediment
那不是障碍
It's great, the other team's velocity is much better than yours, I mean could you guys work late tonight?
很好，但是另一个团队的速率比你们的要好很多，今天你们是不是要加班？
Check it out, the cats are eating a cheeseburger, it can't be healthy at all
来看看，猫儿们在吃芝士汉堡，很不健康